<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Data For Bussinesss on Data For Bussiness</title>
    <link>https://example.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Data For Bussinesss on Data For Bussiness</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 22 Mar 2021 20:20:55 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://example.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>How To Become Data Scientist</title>
      <link>https://example.com/post/chapter-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Mar 2021 20:20:55 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/post/chapter-4/</guid>
      <description>Introduction
Data science is the study of data, it may be structured or unstructured. It involves understanding, extracting values, and visualizing the data. Various machine learning algorithms and statistical methods are used for this. It’s the hottest topic of the 21st century, and the goal of it is to predict information from existing data. Business intelligence (BI) is to make an analysis and report with data, it’s a subset of data science.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Connect to SQL Server and Query Data</title>
      <link>https://example.com/post/chapter-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Mar 2021 20:20:55 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/post/chapter-2/</guid>
      <description>ANSI SQL is the specification that describes the features of any SQL language that is used to query a database. Every database platform I&amp;rsquo;ve ever worked with usually implements a subset of the features of this specification as well as adds some features of their own and SQL Server is no different. The language used to query a SQL Server database is called T-SQL and the commands that make up the T-SQL language can be broken down into a few categories:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kanban - An Introduction</title>
      <link>https://example.com/post/chapter-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Mar 2021 20:20:55 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/post/chapter-5/</guid>
      <description>Scrum addresses the software development where the requirements are frozen before the sprint starts, but what about the teams which work on dynamic requirements which can come at any time?
For example in a team which works on technical tickets, these tickets may come at anytime and hence the sprint cannot be decided, estimation cannot be done and the velocity cannot be calculated.
Kanban is the solution to all this. Started in Toyota, Japan this was introduced to increase the productivity of the factory.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Principles Of Lean Thinking</title>
      <link>https://example.com/post/chapter-6/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Mar 2021 20:20:55 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/post/chapter-6/</guid>
      <description>In my previous article, we learned what is Lean and 5S tools. In this article, we will learn the Principles of Lean Thinking.
Yes, Lean Thinking has principles and they are: Eliminate Waste Amplify Learning Decide as late as possible Deliver as fast as possible Empower the team Build integrity in Optimize the Whole
 Let&amp;rsquo;s dig deeper.
Eliminate Waste
Any activity that consumes resources but adds no value is called waste, in Japanese terms, it&amp;rsquo;s called MUDA; for example, partially done work, extra processes or defects.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SQL Server 101</title>
      <link>https://example.com/post/chapter-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Mar 2021 20:20:55 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/post/chapter-1/</guid>
      <description>By: Ben Snaidero
Overview
Since its initial release in 1989, SQL Server has come a long way from its base functionality as an enterprise level database platform. While the core of SQL Server is still it&amp;rsquo;s database engine, it is now so much more than just a relational database platform. We now have Analysis Services for online analytical processing, Reporting Services for developing reports, Integration Services for developing and running ETL programs as well as many other tools and services that work with and/or support these core components.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Is Data Science?</title>
      <link>https://example.com/post/chapter-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Mar 2021 20:20:55 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/post/chapter-3/</guid>
      <description>By Subham Ray
Introduction
In this article, we will learn about: What is Data Science Top Programming Languages advised for practicing Data Science
What is Data Science?
Data Science is a field that enables users to get the best insights of data that are being delivered to them which may be used to make any decision or to analyze performance or to predict some risk or any outcome based on certain criteria.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://example.com/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/contact/</guid>
      <description>Follow me on these social media platforms.
Platform| URL
YouTube:| https://www.youtube.com/channel/UC_UBIhlTcRysn538I6oxvpQ Twitter:| https://twitter.com/lamtriet5</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
